dubai-online.com 2019-03-17

# Privacy Policy | Dubai Online

## Introduction

This page sets out the privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) of Dubai Online (“We”, “Us”, and “Our”) and explains how We use the data and personal information provided by you (“You” or “Your”) when using this website https://www.dubai-online.com/ (the “Website”). Dubai Online is committed to protecting and respecting Your privacy, and informing You how we use the data and personal information We hold about You.

This Privacy Policy forms part of and is incorporated into our [Terms and Conditions](https://www.dubai-online.com/terms-conditions/ "Website Terms and Conditions") (the “Terms”). By accessing the Website, for whatever purpose, You agree to fully accept these Terms and the Privacy Policy. If You do not agree with these Terms, and/or Our Privacy Policy, do not use the Website.

The Website uses cookies. By using the Website You consent to Our use of cookies in accordance with this Privacy Policy and Our [Cookie Policy](https://www.dubai-online.com/cookie-policy/ "Website Cookie Policy").

This Privacy Policy only applies to this Website. If You leave this Website via a link or otherwise (for example, an advert) to another website, You will be subject to the privacy policy and terms and conditions of that website. We have no control over the privacy policy or the terms and conditions of that website and you should check these before continuing to use that website.

This Privacy Policy applies only to information We collect online. It does not apply to information collected offline.

## Information Collected

We may collect and process the following kinds of information:

  * Data that You provide when completing forms on the Website.
  * If You contact us by email, in writing, or by other means we may keep a record of that correspondence.
  * Details of Your visits to the Website including, but not limited to, traffic data, location data, IP address, operating system, browser, and the resources You access.
  * Information you supply when registering to use restricted areas of the Website.

## Data Transmission and Storage

The transmission of data over the internet is not completely secure. Although We do our utmost to safeguard Your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of Your data transmitted to the Website as no such transmission over the internet or any other public network can be guaranteed to be completely secure. Any transmission is at Your own risk.

Once We have received Your data, We use procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access. All information You supply to Us is stored on Our secure servers. Our servers are located in the United States of America. Payment transactions, if any, will be encrypted.

### Use of Information

We use information held about you in a number of ways, including:

  * Ensuring the content from the Website is presented in the most effective manner for You and Your computer.
  * Improving the Website by collecting feedback we receive from You.
  * Responding to questions, complaints, or requests.
  * Fulfilling any obligations arising out of any contracts entered into between You and Us.
  * Performing statistical analysis of users’ behaviour on the Website.
  * Administering the Website.

### Disclosure of Information

We will not, without Your consent, disclose the personal information You provide to third parties for marketing purposes.

Advertisers and advertising networks use tracking technologies to collect information about Your computer or mobile device and Your online activities. We permit advertisers and advertising networks to collect information when You use the Website to enable them to display targeted adverts to You.

Analytics companies use tracking technologies to collect information about Your computer or mobile device and Your online activities. We permit analytics companies to collect this data when You use the Website.

We do not provide advertisers, advertising networks, or analytics companies with personal information such as your name, address, email address, telephone number, or credit card details.

We may disclose Your personal information to third parties in response to a legal request, such as a court order, to report illegal activity, to enforce Our rights or defend claims. We may also transfer Your data to third party, in the event of the sale of Dubai Online.

### Your Rights

You have the right to ask us for a copy of all Your personal data held by Us and/or any third parties at any time. This request should be made in writing to Our address below. A small charge can be made for this service.

### Variation

Dubai Online may revise the Privacy Policy at any time by amending this page. The Privacy Policy will apply to the use of the Website from the date of the publication of the revised Privacy Policy on the Website. You are expected to check this page before using the Website to take notice of any changes made.

### Contact

Questions, comments and requests regarding this Privacy Policy should be addressed to:

Dubai Online  
6 Stapleton Avenue  
Bolton BL1 5ES  
United Kingdom

02 June 2018
